Okay, so we're going to talk through some slides we're going to look at, and
something
we haven't looked at for a while actually, you know, going back to basics a
little bit,
which is bless you, which is perfect in your profile, so we're going to look at
just a
few things that, you know, it's just a good little refresher, really, and a few
things
that you can do to perfect your profile, maybe get a few more visitors to it,
add to it,
you know, you might see something that you haven't thought of before, but it's
good for
us to have these calls to just sort of inspire each other and get the
inspiration and motivation
to go on, it's a good time of year to review your profile, isn't it, at the
beginning of
the year, and we're also, we'll talk a little bit about, because we've had a
lot of people
asking about their credit balance, so how to work out how many credits they've
got,
and yeah, it's just something that, you know, I mean, I need a refresher on all
the time
because it's not the simplest, so yeah, we'll do a little refresher on how to
understand
your credits and answer some questions about credits that we've had recently,
and so yeah,
let's get started, if you've got any questions, feel free to put them in the
chat or, you know,
just shout them out, that's fine, and we'll come to you at the end who've got
any questions
that you want to ask about anything at all, so let's make a start, so creating
your camp
sauna, so this is just going to go through some of the basics and the first
things that
you're thinking about when you're creating your camp sauna, because you smile
in, is it
because of the picture, Georgia, it's such a nice picture, it's amazing, yeah,
this is
an amazing picture of Chloe from where... Was it the most recent suit? Yeah, I
think so,
it's a recent thing, probably that's just an edited, it's gorgeous, it's so
amazing, so
the first thing you'll be thinking about, and even if you're like on this call
in terms of like
refreshing your profile, these are things that you can change at any time, so
you can refresh
and change these things at any time, so the first things you're thinking about
when you're
thinking about your profile are your name, so your username, which can change
with you
throughout your camp journey, so say you start as, you know, shy girl 23 or
whatever,
you can change it, you know, as you're trying out new things, new niches, you
know, you find
a certain thing that you enjoy doing, you can then put that into your username
so that you're
hopefully attracting the right clients for you, you can also set your age and
your location,
location is a good one and sometimes I think is often forgotten about or
overlooked, is that
you can change your location and it has an impact on the clients that you'll
get, so for instance,
if you've got a London, if you put yourself as a London postcode, you're going
to get a lot more
clients, you know, then if you put yourself in a rural area where there's
probably not going to be
as many people logging on, so this is something to think about if you're a bit
quiet or if you just
want to try something different because you can always change it again and just
thinking about
your location and anything we mention here that you're not quite sure how to do
, you can ask your
mentor and they can help you with it or ask in the group and show somebody or
help you with it as well.
Um, sexual orientation, another one that we don't talk about very much, it's
something that
does impact your profile, so whether you are straight or bi or whatever, it's
really good to
just be as open as you can to give yourself as many opportunities to speak with
as many people
about as many things as possible, so obviously whatever you're comfortable with
, not putting
anything you're not comfortable with, but being open as open as you can is
going to get you the
most clients and the most things to talk about and also your likes, so if you
've seen there's,
there's a list of likes and interest things that you like in terms of your
sexual desires and you
know, things that you, that you like sexually, you know, again, we encourage
you to go through
the list and tick as many of those as you can, it doesn't mean that you're
gonna have to do them,
you know, it just means that you're open to talking about them and people
having fantasies
about them, so you know, a lot of people start off just taking one or two
things, just like modelling
or whatever, but actually, you know, it's all about fantasy, so anything that
you'd be open to
talking about or even listening about someone having a fantasy about, just make
sure that you
tick it because then you're coming up in more searches. Category, so this is
something that you
can change as you go along and just try different things with, so on your web,
on if you go to
edit profile and then to the webcam tab and edit your webcam settings, you can
select different
categories, so you can be in a category, according with your age, 20s, 30s, 40s
, whatever, or you can
be, I think there's a dominant one and there's a couple of different ones, so
yeah, just something
that you can try, if you're having a lull with your profile or you just want to
try something
different, it's always with putting yourself in different categories and seeing
, you know, if you
get some different clients from that, your bio, so your bio is really,
obviously, really
important, so there's another slide where we'll break that down a bit more and
talk about like
how you can make the most of your bio and make it look good, so we'll come back
to that one.
Photos, again, really important, you can be updating these, you know, and
changing them all the time,
so you don't need to be stuck to the same photos, to the same niche or to the
same luck,
but it's really important to have some decent photos because this is, again,
what's going to
draw people into your profile, isn't it? So we recommend for your main profile
picture,
taking up most of the frame just as I am now in this little box so that they
can see you quite
clearly, if you're comfortable with having your face in that picture, then a
nice smiley sort of
approachable face picture is good because that makes them want to connect with
you and see you
as a person, try not to use a photo where you're too far away as your main
picture because it will
just be a tiny little icon that you won't really be able to see, so full length
body photos and
ones where you're a bit further back, a better for your other more general
photos.
Interview, so always, it's always a good idea to fill out the interview, the
AdultWork interview,
so if you go to the My Details page, on there you'll see the AdultWork
interview,
you can also change this at any time, so this is something that I change
sometimes, you know,
it gives your profile a little boost and sometimes you've just outgrown some of
the answers that
you've given on there or you can give better ones, so yeah, answering the
interview with just,
you know, answers that are going to draw the clients in again, just being a bit
flirty or a
bit cheeky or whatever your dynamic is on cam, the interview can be imported,
blogs, so you can
write blogs, this is something I did a little bit in the beginning when I was
trying to establish
myself on cam and I know some girls have had some good traction from them, but
I think, you know,
writing the blogs is just a good way to bring potential clients into your world
, so, you know,
you can talk about what an ideal day you've had or, you know, what you've done
that week or a
blog about a particular part of your life or something else and it's just
another way to sort
of bring your character to life and try to get people engaged with you and to
bulk out your profile
a little bit more and you can always put your, you know, if you're thinking, if
you've written
something and you're not quite sure, you can always, and with any of these, you
know, you're
thinking of making a change and you're not quite sure, it's always a good idea
to browse through
the profiles and have a look at what other people are doing, get some
inspiration or post in the
group, like post in the WhatsApp group and ask us, like, you know, what do we
think and what do we
recommend because you'll always get some good advice from the other members.
And then finally, on this one, the FAQs, so just filling in, if you can, any
frequently
ask questions that you've got because they'll come up on your profile, like,
you don't actually
have to be free, you can frequently ask questions, you don't have to wait until
you've been asked
these questions, you can just use this as another opportunity to sort of sell
yourself and to
engage with people. And so just writing things that you think people might want
to hear,
or they might want to ask you about can be another way to just try and entice
people to engage
for your profile. Okay, and then what will you offer? So obviously, part of
making the most out
of your webcam profile is to think about what services you're actually going to
offer on there.
So we've got some good training about the different, you know, about phone chat
and
texture in particular. See someone's writing in the chat. And yeah, so just
having a think about
the services that you offer, you know, speaking to your mentor, if you want to
think about offering
any other services. Of course, you know, we all start by doing webcam, we can
also do IM, which is
instant messenger, which is basically webcam but without the, without the cam,
without being on
screen. So it's just typing. So that can be great for when you're like out and
about, or you've got
people around you and you can't really can, and you need to be a bit more
discreet. So that can
just bump up your sort of webcam earnings at times when you might not have been
able to can.
Phone chat and text. We've got some training on this in the members area. And
again,
your mentor can help you set that up and get started. And also your private
gallery. So of
course, you can set a price for your private gallery. And you can also, you
know, upload videos or
content that's specifically for a member of your choice. So you can put a pin
code on it and you
can give them the pin code. So you can agree with them in a chat and create
something that's
specifically for that, which helps them to feel a bit more, you know, connected
with you and a bit
more special. Georgia, do you want to do this slide? Yeah. Okay, so how do we
make an eye
catch and profile? So the right photos and always consent. So every time you
upload a new photo or
video to your profile, you have to give consent. Otherwise, it won't upload. So
you basically just
have to consent that you are the only one in the photo. And that obviously you
agree for it to be
shown on there. And yeah, as Elle touched on earlier, when selecting your main
profile photo,
it's very important to select to select the right one. And we're more than
happy to help you choose.
So if you send us over your options, if you're not really sure what to pick, we
can definitely
guide you on what we believe is best, because picking the right one will make
all the difference.
Because when new clients or any, you know, even existing clients are coming to
talk to you,
this is the first thing they see. So as Elle said, if you're all the way in the
background and it's
not really, you know, a close up shot, they're not going to see you much. So
you definitely
want to select one when you look really inviting, really happy or not, depends
on your webcam persona.
I mean, if you're done, maybe you want to look a little bit more mean. So, you
know, just whatever
it is that fits your persona, you want to portray that in your photo. So yeah,
just always bear that
in mind. And also with the photos as well. So it's good to have a few in your
free gallery,
just to give them a little bit more to show you. But then, as in the private
gallery as well,
it's just a no-brainer, because you can make money when you're not even on
there, like literally
make money while you sleep, you can do that with this. And it doesn't need to
be explicit photos,
either. For a while, I just had really tame ones in mind, even photos I put on
Instagram were in there,
that type of, you know, shots, like bikini shots or whatever. Over the years, I
became a little bit
more naughty on there, shall I say. But it's totally at your, you know, your
level, what is
comfortable to you. So your private photos don't even need to be anything that
you would, you know,
consider explicit, they can just be whatever you want. And he can even be
focused on your
feet, you know, because people pay good money for this stuff. And you can
create different albums
and stuff as well. So I'd definitely look into updating your profile with more
photos if you
haven't already, and ones that you can sell. Sorry, I just going to say I'm
that as well. I think
it's always just making a good idea to make sure that you've got a title for
each photo, because I
think they can see the title, can't they for the photo, but not the before they
click and buy the
photo or pay for the photo. So yeah, just making sure that you've got some like
really good teasing
little lines underneath your private photos. Yeah, 100%. Yeah, I've got to
mention that, sorry,
that's true. They see exactly what the caption is. So yeah, if you, the more
you make it look
like, you know, it's a really exciting purchase, the more they're going to buy
it. And then using
tabs and BB codes. So this is for your bio. So instead of your all your bio
just being written
in a huge block of text, you can kind of break it up. And so you can have maybe
an about me,
you can have what I enjoy, you can have what I offer. You know, that's just an
example of
different tabs you could use. So when they click into each one, it gives them
info on each tab,
of course. But you know, you can use any headings for the tabs, whatever would
work with your profile.
And you can also use BB codes and use like little emojis and stuff like that.
So the BB codes
basically change and how your text looks. So it can make it be bold, in italic,
you know,
different fonts, and then also emojis as well. So you can do like little winks
and stuff like that,
a little love heart and stuff, just to make it look a little bit more vibrant
than just plain
text, you know. And so all stuff like this helps highlight as well part of your
profile that you
want more attention on. For example, at the very bottom of my profile, I've had
a day forever. I've
gotten bold to please leave feedback. And there's something else I can't
remember now, but
I feel like it does actually make them look at that and do what I ask because
it's there in bold,
you know. So you can also have an introductory, an introductory movie like I
talk. And so yeah,
this could be nice because obviously still shots are nice. But I think in a
movie, in a video,
you really get to know someone's personality more. Obviously you see there
maybe how they talk,
how they move their mannerisms. So all of this will help your clients connect
to you even more.
And like again, it doesn't need to be anything too crazy. It doesn't need to be
a porn move,
you're anything like that. Can they for sure? If that's what your profile is
like, you know,
and you can definitely charge with this and make great money, or it can just be
something a little
bit more relaxed just to welcome them to your page, let them know a little bit
about you, you know.
You know, it can be 10, 20, 30 seconds. It doesn't need to be something, you
know, really long
and just be something just to draw them in in the beginning. Great idea L.
And so in your profile, you definitely want to highlight your niche and your
personality.
And obviously everyone's profile is going to be a little bit different. And you
actually
want it to be like very specific to you. You don't really want it to be like a
general profile,
which is what we see a lot on there. And some groups when you when you start
with them,
they'll just copy and paste a big massive spiel of text that they put on
everyone's profile.
So it doesn't really give you much personality or individuality. So I think it
's good to
when you do find your niche, really put it on your profile because there's a
market for
everything. And even the more niche you are, I feel as though you've become
very successful
within that niche because there are clients who are after that. And even once
you aren't,
they're curious about that, they're curious about your niche and what you can
offer.
So definitely write it on your profile. And yeah, let your personality come
through as well.
You don't want it to just be like, you know, boring texts like or, you know,
describe and just how
your body looks or whatever else you want it to be about you and your
personality and what you're
bringing to them while you're offering them. And that can be, and that can be
real or it can be
quite fun to be like, you know, to just be like, I'm a teacher or I'm a nurse
or whatever you want
to be. You can just be it. It doesn't need to be about like sexual dessert. You
can just be a bit
having a bit more of a character and just try that on and see if it works and
have fun with it as well.
Yeah, definitely. Like, when I was saying about you, like, it doesn't actually
need like you just
said that it doesn't need to be you. It can be the campus owner that you're
portraying.
So yeah, so if you are portraying pretends and that you're a nurse and you're a
day job on there,
even if you know, like, that's what you used to do right now. And you could
write all about that
on there. And then you can talk to them about your exciting day that you had
and one of your
patients was really hot or whatever else. And probably get your suck, doesn't
it? If you were
saying that stuff, but it's all fantasy anyway. So it's okay. And it's also
nice to talk about
what excites you and what you're curious about on your profile as you know,
this is going to excite
the clients to know that what is exciting you. Because at the end of the day, a
woman in her
pleasure is the most exciting and most beautiful thing. So if they're thinking,
oh yeah, she's
getting excited about this kind of stuff, they're going to be excited by it too
. Trust me. So definitely
write that on your profile. So mention anything that you use or do and this
could be games or
Lovense. So a lot of our members have gotten to this Lovense craze, which
is great because it's
it really helps on parm. It's helping people make even more money because
people have to tip
to make this Lovense wake up. So the Lovense is basically a toy. They have
all different
ones you can choose from. You can connect it to your cam and it comes up online
like the clients
can see that you have a Lovense and then they can tip you to then make the
toy wake up and vibrate
and whatever else and for them for you to then potentially use it. So if you if
you have one of
these, definitely definitely mention it on your profile. And if you don't have
one and you're
interested, I would 100% recommend looking into it and getting one because it's
it's the girls have
had a lot of success with this. But yeah, outside of that, I just mentioned
anything that you do.
I know one of our girls, she does games sometimes and she had like a spin the
wheel that she made,
that she would play with clients. So it doesn't always have to be, you know,
sexual stuff like
with regard to what you do, it can be anything, you know. And so stuff like
that will really make
you stand out and having that written on your profile will do the same. And so
yeah, so maybe
have a little think about, you know, creative games that you can play and could
even play like,
you know, sexy card games. I'm not really sure what that would be right now,
but you can think of
something like, you know, if a sit number comes up, you have to do something if
something else comes
up, they have to do something or they have to tip you even better. And so, you
know, stuff like that,
just give it a bit more fun, a bit more personality to your profile.
Okay. And remember to write it for your ideal client. So you can't be everyone
's cup of tea,
but you can be someone's class of champagne. Love that. And so yeah, like don't
write on there,
like, you know, that you're going to be doing this, this and this, even though
you know, deep down,
you don't really want to do that. That's not really you. Be honest on there
about what you want to
offer, about what you offer and, you know, who you want to attract. And you
genuinely will.
We were talking earlier about the name change as well. This is important for
also attracting
the right clients. I've done domination on there the whole time since I've been
on there.
I do what my fingers as well don't get me wrong, but I do really like to do
domination.
And in the past, I just had a general username. I think it was, it was Ruby
something. But now,
it's well, I changed it to Goddess Ruby halfway through. And now it's Goddess J
because I put myself
on Instagram on there. So just put my G on there for me. But anyway, since I
changed to Goddess,
I noticed so many more subs were coming through because it was literally in my
username. Like,
it couldn't, you couldn't miss it that I do domination because anyone who's
into domination
knows that you call your, you call them mistress or Goddess or something like
that. So when they'd
see Goddess, they come straight to me, all the subs. So this is that I was
writing that for my
ideal clients, you know, I changed my username for my ideal clients. And it
worked. So, so yeah,
don't be worried about like honing in on a niche and just really thinking about
who do I want to
attract and writing the profile for them. And then you will attract that, you
know. But yeah,
is anything else you would add to this one? Oh, there's a little bit left,
sorry. And finally,
you can take inspiration from other profiles and let your profile grow and
change with you.
So as I just said that, I let you just change mine and to grow with me, even
though I did always
do domination, the more I got comfortable in there, the more established I
thought, I need to really
make my profile way more dominant, like domination vibes and it helped. And
yeah, taking inspiration
from others, this is totally fine to do. I still do this after all this time on
there.
And because, you know, there might be one little thing that they write that it
might not even be
that that you take else, which then you think, Oh, I can write this or I can
have this or I definitely
don't want that, you know. And so yeah, like whenever you're just waiting for
calls or before,
or even before you log on, just have a little browse of the girls online,
especially with the
ones with a lot of feedback, they're likely to be done there for a while and
got established profiles.
And even the ones who haven't, I suppose, because you never know, maybe even
the ones who don't
have still got great profiles. And yeah, just take a little look through, see
what you like,
and yeah, just note down anything that you want to add to yours. But yeah, that
's what I would say
on that is anything you want to add, Elle? And about it, really, I think, I
think just not being
scared to change your profile, you know, because we, I'm sure you and I have
changed
ours many times and seeing many members change them many times. And like, just,
I'm also taking
inspiration from your clients, like just noticing, like, what type of clients
do you normally get,
even when you're not trying to, even when you're not an initial, whatever, like
, what,
is there a common theme there? And if so, can you put that on your profile? Is
it, can you put,
like, oh, you know, I fancy doing this, like, I, for a while, I was at a common
theme for me,
was that I was getting loads of guys that wanted to do, like, forced by,
because I think, I don't
know if it was a bit of a trend, or I don't know if it's something to do with
me, who knows, but
I thought, okay, I'll, I'll follow you. Yeah. I like a new to that a little bit
in my profile,
then, like, and that was good, because I got a load of people asking me about
it.
So yeah, just taking inspiration from other profiles is good, but also from
your clients
about, you know, what type of clients come into you already, so then you can
just tap into that a
bit better. Okay. So, bringing in traffic, so, you know, we all, you know, want
to bring in traffic
to our profiles, don't we? Obviously, the newer that you are, well, I see this,
actually, I was
going to say the newer, the newer you are, the less, the less develop your
profile is, the less
traffic you're going to get, not always the case. I mean, I think you can get a
lot of traffic just
by being a new person, because, you know, the clients love a new beyond there,
don't they?
But I think you can also get a bit of a lull sometimes, which puts some people
off and they,
you know, feel a bit crap about, which happens to me, and I've seen it happen
to so many people,
where when you first get on, you get like, you get, you're busy, because you're
the new person on
there, everyone's intrigued, and then after a little while, it fizzles out a
bit, and then you're
like, oh God, like, it's not as busy as it was before, maybe I've lost it, like
what's going on,
but I think there can be just a bit of a lull, and then that's when it's the
important time to do
all these things, you know, to do all the things you can to boost your profile
as much as you can,
so that you can get regulars, and once you've got decent regulars then, you
know, you'll never
get too quiet, you know, if they're loyal to you. So, of course, the basics is
positioning,
we call it positioning, we also call it bidding or boosting, you see the little
boost button next,
you know, when you're on camera, so you can boost by the hour, and it will
prompt you now, which is
great, and never used to do that, it will prompt you to boost for the hour,
which will give you
exposure for the hour, speak to your mentor, if you're not sure about this, or
want to know a bit
more about it. I do this every time, pretty much every time I go on, I mean, I
do have
regulars that have been loyal for years, so they do tend to come back, but I
still bid,
because I just don't like to sit there, and it's quiet, so yeah, there's that,
then there's
featuring, so featuring is similar to bidding, but you're doing it for the
whole day,
rather than just by the hour, and it's a lot cheaper, and so it tends to be
around 12 credits,
I think you can get it for, it goes up or down depending on how busy it is,
like what time of
it, what day it is, if it's a weekend, and how far in advance you're featuring,
so you can feature
for, I think it's two, two weeks, it might be a bit more than that, in advance,
and the more in
advance you do it, the cheaper it is, I used to do it all the time, and I used
to really enjoy it,
that's when I was on cam all the time, so I'd know that I've got the full day
to do it,
these days I rarely have the whole day to sit on cam, so I don't do it as much,
but if I know I'm
gonna have that all day, then I will do, and I do find it quite good. Free chat
, obviously,
you know, we talk about this a lot, some members, love it, other members, not
so much,
it's just that these things are all about your preferences, but it's worth
trying all of them,
just so you know, you know, how it is for you, and if it's going to bring in
clients for you.
Special offers, so that's what this picture is on the right here, is how the
screen shows up to
put a special offer on, so yeah, you can put a special offer on which will come
up on your profile,
which they can then book, which is just sort of encouraging your clients, as it
says, to book in
for prepaid sessions, so they've got a fixed length, so you can say you're
gonna do a certain thing,
you can tie it into a fetish, or like an outfit you're gonna wear, or maybe a
dance, you know,
I know a couple of our members have like a pole or whatever, so yeah, that's
the next
year thing that just to entice people in that you can put on your profile, you
can also do this,
like if you've got budding regulars or someone you really enjoy chatting with,
you know, it can
be a nice way to kind of connect and flirt and be like, okay, I'm gonna put
enough on there,
just for you, I'm gonna surprise you with what it is, so come and have a look
tomorrow and you know,
see what, see what offer I've got for you, and so it can be a way to like,
solidify those regulars
and make them feel a bit special, you can say the same thing to like, 10 people
obviously,
but to them you're always saying it just to them, you can recommend your
friends, I think, I think
when I wrote that I thought, oh yeah, we should talk about this more because I
know that some of us
do this already, or quite a lot of us do this already, so if I'm chatting to
someone and they
chat to me for ages and they're really keen, then I'll be like, oh yeah, I was
just with my friend
blah blah blah, and we were doing this or that like, tell a little sexy story,
like she's she's on
cam as well, and just give the username and they'll search and go talk to the
person,
they love the things that they're like, in your life, like, on the inside, like
, oh yeah,
spoke to blah blah blah, like, you know, yeah, we have the honest looks between
me and you, right?
Yeah, I think we've had a few over the years, I'm way like,
and they love to take it in our little friendship group, like you are, I'm sure
petting you are.
Yeah, I know, I know. I'll be actually a piece of that one.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, and other people as well, like, we've had a bit of a back and
forth, or if I'm
chatting to a client, I think, oh, they're gonna like, such and such, and I'll
just
summon these, a name and say to say hello, and that's my friend or whatever, so
it's a good way
to get, to share your good regulars with other people. And then Twitter or X,
now it still says
Twitter and AdultWork, that's why I put Twitter, but you can link your Twitter
or X profile with
your AdultWork, so that you can post and get clients from there, you can set
it up, so I think,
so it automatically posts on X every time you get a tip or have a call over 10
minutes or something
like that. There's a few different options, so that's if you're, you know, if
you're public about
it, and you can build up a following elsewhere that you can also bring over to
here, which some
girls do. Being heartlisted, of course, this is like really important, like
anyone that's going
to be a regular will have you heartlisted. It's the only way that they're going
to consistently
be able to see you. They're going to get, you know, a notification when you
come online,
so making sure if you've had a really long chat with someone, it's been really
good just asking
them to heartless you. And it doesn't have to be a hard sell, it can be like, I
've loved our chat
today, like, please, we are heartless to me, so you know what, I'm on next, I'd
love to chat to you
again. And similarly, replying to emails, so if you're quiet, and you're just
sat there waiting
for calls, always go through your emails. I know that I sometimes let mine
build up because I'm just
like busy on cam, and then I'll go on, and I haven't got a call straight away,
and I'll look on, I've
got like 40 emails, I'm like, wow, I really should have been keeping up with
those, but yeah, replying
to your emails, again, it's just another way to keep those relationships going,
isn't it?
And as we always say, not too much detail in your replies, because you don't
want to be spending
lots of time on them, and then they're getting your attention for free, you
just want to be
checking in with them and asking them to come on cam, or telling them when you
're next online.
Anything you'd add to that change, I think now should I breathe in before
bringing in traffic?
Yeah, I feel so. Yeah, you're covered if.
Okay, do you want to do this? Yeah, so getting regulars, so as Elle just said,
what she's forgetting to do is answer your emails. This does help. Sometimes
though,
they just want to speak to you back and forth on email, so just be aware of
that.
Obviously, don't speak to them too much on email before they do a pay chat,
but definitely people do express interest on email, because a lot of the time
as well,
they'll have very specific things that they want to chat about in cam, so they
're emailing you first,
just to double check that it's okay for them to speak to you about this. So
with ones like that,
you can definitely reply and seem interested in what they like, if you are, of
course,
if you do want to offer them that. And then just direct them to your private
chat.
And then of course, in between sessions, so when you've already got a regular
email,
it's a good way to keep in touch with them to organise the next session.
So yeah, it can be really good to all the emails for sure.
And then another thing actually as well is if you come back to Cam after some
time away,
you instead of just replying to emails you already got, you can go back through
your old ones
to find like previous regulars and email them and say, "Hey, I've been away for
a little bit,
but now I'm back." Just to reopen that again. So yeah, the emails can be great.
Another good thing for getting regulars is writing details down about them.
So like, note it down. So honestly, they just all want to feel like you've
remembered them
and you've remembered those small details about them, about obviously, you know
, their daily life,
about what their dog's name is, about what type of food they like or, you know,
what their sexual
preferences is, like, you know, down to everything. It's not like if you try to
remember as much as
possible about them and bring it up in future sessions, future sessions will
definitely go
a long way for you. Because honestly, sometimes you could have like so many
kinds that you're talking
to and then they're coming back and then they're like, "Oh yeah, I just want to
do what we've done
last time." And you're like, "Ah, what did I do last time?" Like, this has
happened so many times
for me. And I'm like, "Right, I need to just take my own advice and write it
all down."
So I will genuinely now do. I have a list on my phone, all the user names I
speak to and a
quick little note next to each one. I literally do it while I'm in the chat,
just so it's done,
just so I remember. Then at the end of the call, you could go back to it then
and write down more
details. But it does really go a long way because at the end of the day, they
're paying for a
connection. They're paying for your time, your energy. So the more you're going
to make them feel
important, the more they're going to keep going back to you. They've just spent
a lot of money
with you, a lot of time, money and energy. And then they come back the week
later and you don't
have a clue who they are, you don't remember. Which is fair enough because we
talk to a lot of people
then they're going to be like, "Oh, she didn't even remember me." Whereas if
you then
remember something about them, they're going to love that and they're going to
keep coming back
and you want to make them feel special. And don't just think, "Oh, yeah, I'll
remember that."
Because you probably... Well, if you're anything like me, you won't because you
'll have then somebody
else that comes in, that your focus goes on them and you forget what you've
just done with the previous
one. So just write it down. Just save yourself a bit, the hassle of trying to
remember all these
different people and just write it down. And then you will start to remember,
of course,
then over time, the more they come back, you know, once they become a proper
solid regular,
you won't need... You know, you don't need to write it down so much because you
know them.
But especially in the beginning, it helps you remember sitting, details about
sitting people.
And so to come out regular times as well as good because you're building up
regulars
in that time slot. So I remember I was coming a lot in the days and I just got
a lot of
the clients who are in work and they're like, you know, coming on their lunch
break or just
coming anywhere, like even, you know, working or whatever, their bosses around.
And that was
good because there was those ones that were quite tame, quite like those calls
because they couldn't
do much. It was more about just talking about the fantasy of stuff. So yeah, so
I always have
those regulars that were those business professionals because I was coming in
those hours.
So yeah, and then they always knew as well what times to come to me. They knew
I'd be on these
certain times because I would always be on those times. And you can even,
actually, I don't know if
you can do it anymore. They've been a bit funny with it. You used to be able to
write on your profile
when you'd be online. But I don't know now, I don't want to say because they've
changed,
they've changed you recently. Because you can still set your availability.
Okay, perfect. You like the tick sheet that says what, what days you're on and
times?
Okay. Yeah, maybe. Yeah, maybe they just wanted you to do it that way rather
than the profile.
Right. Yeah. Yeah, because I used to have written on there the times I'd go on.
This was years
ago now. But then I remember one of our members done it and recently and it
wasn't allowed. But
yeah, but they have their own function for this. So you could just go on to add
it work, go to the
availability. But this is if you know, obviously your regular times and you can
put in there,
they can take exactly what hours you're going to be online over the next few
days or next week.
And that just helps if your regulars know and when to catch you. And if you don
't want to put
that on there, if you don't know fully, you can always just email your regulars
again,
and she'll be like, ah, I'm going to be on Thursday, nine to 11 Friday, blah,
blah, blah, blah.
You know, hope to see you at one of those, at one of those times, you know.
And as Elle already mentioned, ask clients who you enjoyed to hot list you.
This honestly
goes the longest way. And this is how I feel like I can go online after not
being on there for a
while. And I still got, I got a call more or less right away. It's because I'm
in many hot lists
after so long on there. So, and we all have to build it up and start somewhere.
So even if
you're brand new and you're not on many hot lists, time is going to pass anyway
. So you may as well
in that time, try and get on as many as possible. And as the time goes on more
and more, you're
going to be in hundreds of guys hot lists. So it's hard to not be busy when you
're in hot lists.
So, yeah, I'd definitely recommend asking your clients. Like you Elle said,
doesn't need to be
like a, you know, a forceful thing. You can just be like a cute little thing at
the end. Like,
oh, I really enjoyed our time together. Would love to chat to you again. Would
love if I was
in your hot list so we can connect easier next time. And you can know when I'm
online, you know,
something like that. And yeah, it's great. Just try getting as many hot lists
as possible.
And so as for feedback and give it in return, this is also a really great point
. And the more
feedback you have on your profile, the better. And if you're giving feedback to
your clients,
it might then spark them to give it to you. And it just means that your
profiles are there in
more places, the more feedback you give, the more obviously your, you know, the
more you're out there.
So yeah, I ask my clients, I know some people don't like to, but I do. I ask my
clients to give me
feedback. You can always ask them on the chat or even on email afterwards. Or
you can just mention
it on some stage, especially if you know, you can just say, oh, I'm new. I'm
really just trying
to build up my feedback and build up my profile. You know, if you enjoy our
chat today, I really
appreciate if you could leave me some feedback at the end. Because I like to
know that they're
helping you as well, you know. And yeah, as we also previously mentioned, you
can upload content
just for them. So you can set a little code on sitting videos or albums that
can be only
accessed by them. And then they can also still pay for this. So it's not like
it's just a free,
you know, free thing for them. I mean, you could if they've been really
generous in the chat and
they're coming to you time and time again, you could reward them with a little
album of a few
photos or videos or whatever in there for free because they're coming back week
in, week out,
spend a lot of money. That definitely will go a long way, for sure. If you're
noticing that and
giving them something for free, they're going to love that. Or if not, you can
also just charge
as well, of course, if it's not one that spends as much, maybe definitely
charge them. Because
regardless whether they're getting charged for it or not, because it's a folder
just for them,
even if it's not, they're going to feel special. And we all like to feel
special, right? So,
yeah, I guess I want to go.
Hey. Thank you, Jay. Okay, so just a few things then to
think about upkeep of your profile. Because of course, you know, it's as we
said a few times,
it's ever-changing, you know, it's something that you're going to develop over
the years.
I don't think I'll ever get to a 0.1 profile as done. You know, I never want to
get to that point,
because I always want to be like improving and changing and just adapting,
depending on what
clients I've got and what I want to do at the time. So yeah, as we've said,
just being consistent
or being consistent on cam, but also with your profile, you know, so there are
a few other things
that you can do to stay consistent with your profile is changing your strap
line.
So in your edit profile webcam on the webcam tab, there'll be the webcam
setting. So in there,
you can change your category, as it says, try different categories and also
change your strap
line. So this is something I do every time I go on. And I just say a little
thing about what I'm
wearing or where I am, or like, you know, like horny lunch break or whatever,
just a little thing about right now so that they know I've updated it.
Adding to or changing your bios, even if you're just changing a couple of lines
or point
some punctuation in, this can help give you a boost. So it's always good to
just have a look
over and see if there's anything to add quickly. Setting your availability, as
we've said, so you
can use that. There is a feature on there from the My Details page where you
can set the availability.
You can just do it for the week ahead if you know what you're going to be on
for that week.
Adjusting your rates accordingly. So this is something that can be really
important, actually,
because, you know, we'll all have times where we might have a little bit of a
lull, you know,
it might be a bit quiet and it can get really disheartening. Like, if you go on
once or twice
and you're hardly getting any calls, then adjusting your rates can be really
important.
So having a quick look at who else is online and what prices they are on and
who's, you know,
in a call and who's not, and you might need to just lower your prices a little
bit, you know,
when you're quieter. And then, you know, I will always, if I get, if I've got a
couple of good
regulars on the go, or if I've got someone who I know is really hooked, then I
'll put my prices up
because I know that they're going to come back. I know it's not going to phase
them. So, yeah,
lowering and increasing your prices, depending on how busy you are, it's just
good business,
you know, and it helps you to always get an income coming in. Uploading new
content, as we said,
this is always a boost, you know, like George was saying, even if it's a
picture of your feet,
or, you know, you out for a meal or something, you know, whatever, it's always
good to update it.
And using the profile wizard feature, so this is something I do sometimes. If
you go to my details,
there is a bit where it says profile wizard and it will tell you what more you
could do
to get the most out of your profile. So, it might be stuff you don't want to do
,
it does say things like you could put phone chat on or whatever, if you don't
want to do that,
obviously, don't do that. But it does sometimes give some good tips about what
you could do.
So, yeah, it's always worth just having a look at that, especially if you're
quiet,
because it can give you tips on your profile. And sometimes it has a little
like red
warning or whatever, and it will say that you need to do something. It might
tell you you need
to consent on some of your pictures because we're not showing up or something
like that.
Sometimes it has a really useful tip that, you know, so it's worth looking at
and just making sure your profile is the best it can be.
Where is the profile wizard? I'll confirm it after this. I just, I had a look
at it earlier,
actually, because when I was like looking at this and I was like, oh, yeah, I'm
gonna have a look
at mine now. It's really easy to find. I want to say it's in the edit profile,
and I think it's on the right-hand side on that list there, but I'll have a
look.
And I'll paste it in the group after this. But yeah, it's quite easy to find,
and it's a useful feature.
Yeah, so we're going to go on and talk about the credits a little bit.
But does anyone have any questions or any anything that they want to add about
their
profile that's helped or anyone else has got anything that we might not have
covered?
There's nothing else that I can think of really. It's always good to go.
Yes, same covers a lot.
Yeah, okay. Okay, let's move on then.
So understanding your earnings. So we thought we'd do this on the call today
because we've got
it in our welcome course and also your mentor talks you through it. And we've
got a video on
it as well, but it's still one of the things that is always good to come back
to and go over again,
because I think people, myself included, maybe slip into bad habits and just
start looking at
their credits on one screen and have been like, "Oh, why is that not right?"
Because you need to check your credits in the right way to know how much you're
making.
So we're just going to go over a few credit, a bit of a credit information and
how you work
out your credits and things. So we can refer people to this call as well. So we
've got a nice
current recent call that we've done a little bit about credits on.
Yeah, do you want to talk about this? Not a lot to talk about, yeah.
So the credit breakdown. So one credit to OZ is 56 pence, 56.5 to be exact, but
obviously
we don't have 0.5. So yeah, 56 pence is one credit for OZ. So obviously if you
make 100 credits,
that's 56 pounds, 50 pence and so on. So out of your credits, the ECC takes 10
%. Payroll takes
3.5% and AdultWork takes 30%, but I will mention if you are on your own and
not on a group,
AdultWork would take 36% from you. So being a part of the group, AdultWork
take less from you,
which is really good. Oh yeah, you've wrote that there. So working all that out
,
even though you're paying 10% towards and 3.5 to pay roll, so ends up being 13.
5%. If you're
minus off the 6% that AdultWork, don't take from you because you're with us.
It means you're only
paying 7.5% overall to be with the ECC and receive everything that we offer and
also the daily pay.
So yeah, it's not so bad when you look at it that way.
Okay, so to work out what you've made, so you subtract the amount you started
on from the
amount that you end on. So let's say we look at our credit statement and we've
ended the day
on 200 credits, then you might think, oh, I've made 200 credits a day, but then
when you actually
look, we'll look into this more a little bit later, but then when you actually
look,
you actually start at that day on 120 credits because they were previous
credits that are still
in your balance from days before. So you might see the 200 and think, oh, I've
made that, but
yeah, you have made that, but that was accumulation over a couple of days or a
couple of weeks or
whatever. So if you go back to the very start of the day and you see it started
on 120,
you have to do 200, what you ended on, take away 120, what you started on, and
that will obviously
leave you with 80. So that means you've earned 80 credits that day. Now, as we
know, 80 credits,
we then need to work out what that is in pounds. So to calculate what you've,
what it is in pounds,
is you will times that 80 credits by 0.56, or what I do is, which is basically
the same,
is I will type in, so I'll do that on the calculator now just to show you. So
80 times 0.565 equals
45/20, so that means you've earned 45 pounds 20 pence on that day. So the way I
do it is,
it's the same, but just a different method. So 80, take away 43.5 cent, and
then equals
same 45 pound 20. I do it, it's just the same way of doing it. Like I take away
43.5% because
that's the percentage that's taken. As we said, 30 goes to AdultWork, 10
towards 3.5 to daily pay.
So yeah, you can do it either way, times it by that, or take away 43.5%
whatever floats your boat.
So remember, payroll with drawer credits that you've already been paid. So the
overall balance
might not be right, so it's what I've just said. And also, the balance that's
on your
come screen. So when you're coming, and you see yourself on the screen, you see
all your
clients using names and how much they've spent, and you've got your little
total.
That's not the correct total, and this is where a lot of members go wrong. They
say what they
believe they've made that day, and then they pay the difference amount the next
day. So let's say
you've been coming, and it says you've earned 100 credits, and then the next
day you don't get paid
what 100 credits would be, and you're like, hmm, why is that? It's because you
're looking at the wrong
screen. So you have to go into your credit statement to see what you've made,
because
the screen that you're coming on, it doesn't account for the small charges that
add a work take.
So as well as the 30% that they take, they take a small charge for each call.
It's called a faculty
fee. So it's not much, it's a very, very small amount that they take from each
call. But this
adds up, of course. So that could add up to 10 credits with. So then you've not
been paid for 10
credits with that you thought you should have been paid for, and then we get
people messaging
us, worried about the pay, you know, saying that they've been underpaid, but an
actual fact they
haven't, so they just haven't worked it out properly. So it isn't okay, want to
look at when you're
coming, you know, to see how much is on there, because it's going to be close
to that. So it says
you've made 100 credits, maybe you've actually made 95 or 90, so it's close. It
's close to what it says,
but it's not the same amount. So you can look at that, you know, and be like,
yeah, I'm doing well,
and see what you're making, because like I said, it's not far off that, but don
't look at that
for the exact amount, because it's definitely not. The exact amount is found on
your credit
statement, which we'll take a look at next. It's really frustrating that they
do that. It's like,
why don't they just show on the screen that you're coming, what you're actually
getting.
I know it would save you. There's a lot of hassle after a short,
save you girls for a hassle worrying about, you know, thinking of being onto
paid and stuff.
But we can find it on the credit statements as shown here. So this is a
screenshot of a credit
statement. Obviously it can look quite overwhelmed, and even to meself, I'm
like, oh,
how am I going to explain this? Yeah, it could be quite overwhelming, so I'll
explain.
So, okay, so that when you're working on your credits, you always have to think
, when was the
last day was I paid? So let's say you were last paid on the 23rd of the 1st. So
let's take a look
at that on the screen here. So that's when you were last paid by payroll. So
anything you've made
after that is what you owed. So this is how you'll work out work. So to work
out what you've made
on each day, of course, as we said, you start off by subtracting what you
started the day on to
what you finished the day on. That's how you work out what you've made on any
given day. We've
already explained that. But to work out what you've made from the last time you
've been paid,
that's another way of doing that. And I'll explain that now. So you might have
been paid on a set day,
comes a little bit, but not made enough for the to be paid because you have to
make 90 credits to
be paid the next day. So if you haven't made that, it's going to sit in your
balance, and then you
can work a little bit more to then push it over there. So let's see how to work
out what we've been
paid since the last time we were paid. So we're going to say for argument's
sake that we were last
paid on the 25th of the first on this credit statement. So we'll have a look at
that and see
what we ended the 25th of the first on. So we ended that day on 13.23 credits.
So keep that in mind.
So anything made after that is what you've made. Obviously what you should be
paid on the next one
when you've pushed over your balance. So if you have a little look straight
away, that goes down
because someone's been paid for positioning. And then a few credits are made, a
little bit more
of paper for position and then a nice amount is made. So let's just say, let's
ignore the last two.
So let's just say we want to know what we've made from the 25th to the 28th,
because
let's just do the whole screen, actually, let's just say we'll just see what we
made from the 23rd
all the way until the 29th. So you'll do 182.83. Take away what we started,
what we ended with on
the 23rd, because we got paid that day. So anything from then onwards. So take
away 13.23. So that
equals 169.6. So that's how many credits that you've made since the 23rd. And
then to work out what
that is in pounds, you can times it by 0.565 or take away 43.5%. So then you're
left with 95
pounds, 28, 95 pounds, 82 tons. So yes, that's how you work it out. Does anyone
have any questions?
I know that it's a bit complicated. So I can answer any questions if anyone has
.
No. And just remember as well, I never can look quite daunting, or the easiest
way to look at it is
just subtract what you started the day on from what you ended it on, or
subtract from when you
were last paid the last date what that was to what the date is now, because it
might not be just
over one day, it might be a few days of earning money for you to then get the
payout. So just
always go back through your bank statements and say, Oh yeah, I was last paid
on this date.
So I know that from whatever I've made on this date, like whatever. Sorry. So
you know, look for
your bank statements. Let me just rewind. Look for your bank statements. See,
oh yeah, I was last
paid on the 17th. Let's say now it's the 20th. So you've got three days there
where you'll be making
credits that you quote, work out what you've made. So it's not just obviously
working out what you've
made on each day. In this case, it'll be work out what you've made in the last
three days,
which then you'll be paid the next day if it's pushed over the minimum. So yeah
, I know it can
be a little bit complicated, but we are always here to help. And if you have
any worries about
your pay or anything like that, just reach out to one of us and we will look
into it. And if you have
ever been paid incorrectly, you will be paid every penny that you're owed. So
never worry about
that. So if you do believe you've been on the paid, which like I said, a lot of
time, it's not,
it's just like the credit to being calculated wrong. So if you ever do feel
that you have,
don't worry. We'll work it out. And if it is definitely, if it is definitely
wrong and you
have been on the paid, you will get paid. Trust me. And like I said, a lot of
the time is just
because it's not being calculated properly. And I can always explain, you know,
I can always explain
it because sometimes girls have been like, Oh, I think I've been on the page
and I've been like,
Oh no, it's actually right. I'm going to show you now. And then I've explained
it to them.
And I believe that they've definitely like, you know, seen that. Oh yeah,
actually that is right,
you know. And so yeah, I can definitely help explain it in a way that will make
sense.
Because trust me, still after 10 years, I still have to like sit there and
scratch me head like,
Oh, is this right or wrong? But we get bit in the end. And so yeah, I hope that
makes sense.
Oh yeah, someone just wrote in the chat. Okay. Thank you, Jay. I know that's,
you hadn't even looked at that slides or that example. So thank you for doing
that.
Um, off the top of your head. Yeah, I appreciate it. And I do want a daily
basis. So it's all right.
I've got a lot of practice. Look on our clouded statements.
Well, so have I, but it doesn't, it doesn't make me, it doesn't make me any
better about it.
Um, okay. And just a few final little things to mention, you know, while we're
on credits.
Um, just to let us know ASAP, if you change your username or bank details, then
we'll need to let
payroll know so that they've got the up-to-date information for you. Also, if
you haven't been
online for ages, sometimes you go inactive on their system because they're, you
know, day by day,
they're manually paying everyone. So yeah, if you haven't been online for ages
and you're,
you haven't got, you're wondering why your payment hasn't, it's the first day
you've been back on,
you're wondering why you've not paid your payment yet. Just give us a nudge and
we can just give them
a nudge. Um, so those, yeah, those things. And as, as G said, if you think you
've been under or
overpaid or whatever and you've had a little look, you've worked it out or you
're not quite sure,
just speak to your mentor or one of us and we can have a look for you and
contact payroll for you,
too. Um, and also if you want to be paid weekly or monthly, that's something
that can be arranged
as well. I was just trying to think of anything else that, that we can let you
know about credits
and I think that's it, really. Um, maybe one thing that we didn't mention,
which, you know,
maybe is obvious anyway, but on the credit statement, it will also show, like,
if you bid,
if you bid to put yourself on the front page, if you spent money on bidding,
that will come off
the, on the credit statement. So you'll be able to see that there. You'll be
able to see any charges
and everything is clearly laid out on the credit statement, but that, that will
be one of those
things that might, that you wouldn't see on the main page while you're coming
is anything that
you've spent on bidding as well. Um, so yeah, I think that's it. I think that's
it. Um, does anyone
have anything they want to add or any questions? Actually, while you were
looking at that, I just
quickly had a look where the, um, where that thing was that I was talking about
earlier. So if you go
to my details and edit profile, then click on edit profile and it has a little
drop down list.
So that's where the profile wizard is. Um, it's also got, I think, profile
health. I couldn't really
see much difference between either of those. I think they're pretty much the
same thing that
you can have a look at them. And there's also from the My Details page, there's
also Business Builder
thing on the bottom left. If you click on Business Builder, again, it's a
similar thing. It will
just give you some tips on how you could build your business and anything you
might not have done
that you can do to sort of promote yourself a bit more. So yeah, just some
little tools on the
website that are useful. Um, no worries, no worries. Thanks for the question.
Um, so yeah, I think,
I think that's it for us from today. I thought we'd given you a little bit of
inspiration. Um,
and yeah, if there's anything that you, you know, if you, if you've seen
anything and you do it after
today, please let us know. Like, we'd love to know if you, you know, have
changed something in your
profile or you've like taken something from today's call when it, and it helps
you, we'd love to know.
Um, so feel free to message about all one of those and let us know. Um, and
yeah, as always,
you know, let us know if there's any particular training that you'd like as
well. This is like,
you know, we're often doing the training because it's been asked with somebody
's asked for a
particular type of training. So yes, let us know if we've got any requests. Um,
yeah, if anybody's
going on camp tonight, I hope you have a good night on camp. Um, and we'll see
you very soon.
Thank you everyone. See you soon. Bye ladies. Bye ladies.